cisdata.net 2014-06-06

# Privacy Policy | iHOUSEweb, Inc.

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This privacy policy applies to the iHOUSEweb, Inc website and other Internet-accessible iHOUSEweb, Inc services. Please note that this policy applies only to iHOUSEweb, Inc websites, and not to other companies’ or organizations’ websites to which we link from our products. 

### 1\. How We Use Your Information

Your information once collected is never sold, traded or bartered with any third party companies. The information you supply to us is used by our staff and trusted partners only. 

### 2\. Information About You

Additionally, we may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service, or when you request information. We will need certain information — such as name, email address etc., in order to provide that service or information to you. We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested. We may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium, but you may always choose to respond or not. We also use cookies or server-side session technology in order to improve your experience, including to remember your preferences or customized settings when you use iHOUSEweb, Inc websites and its related services, and to authenticate your access to your personal information. 

### 3\. Information About All iHOUSEweb, Inc Visitors

In general, our websites automatically gathers certain usage information like the numbers and frequency of visitors to iHOUSEweb, Inc websites. We only use such data in the aggregate. This aggregate data helps us determine how much our clients use parts of the website, so we can improve our website to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of you as possible. For example, iHOUSEweb, Inc uses a technology called “cookies” that tells us how and when pages in our website are visited, and by how many people; the use of cookies is an industry standard and is practiced by most major Web sites. These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through these cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are. 

### 4\. Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We periodically review and update these security measures. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be one hundred percent (100%) secure. As a result, although we strive to protect a visitor’s personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us or from our online products or services, and visitor does so at his/her own risk. 

### 5\. Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, and to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we never collect or maintain information at our web site from those we actually know are under the age of thirteen (13), and no part of our web site is structured to attract anyone under the age of thirteen (13). Questions regarding the above statement should be directed to info(at)ihouseweb.com 

### 6\. Your Acceptance of This Policy

Your use of this website and Services offered by iHOUSEweb, Inc will constitute acknowledgment of and agreement to this policy and Terms of Service. iHOUSEweb, Inc may revise this policy in part or in full at any time without notice to the client. If you do not agree to this policy, do not use the iHOUSEweb, Inc Service.
